VLATKO MICEVSKI



Contact

Address:

Str. Bataljon Stiv Naumov 9/25, 7000 Bitola North Macedonia

Phone:

+389 79 324 191

Email:

vlade83@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/vlatko-micevski-b0a2a6177

Languages

- Macedonian C2
- ➤ English C2
- ➤ German B2
- ➤ Greek–A2

Technical Experience

- Asykuda
- Kasper
- Microsoft Office package

Hobbies

- Cooking
- Fitness
- Judo
- Boxing

Summary

A highly motivated and experienced customs broker. Excellent admin skills, good knowledge of all Microsoft Office programs, Asykuda, Kasper, as well as proficiency in English. Flexibility, agility, and extensive experience liaising with clients and colleagues. Fully committed to continuing my career on a full-time basis in your company as we work together towards greater achievements.

Skill Highlights

- Good communication skills
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Leadership skills

Attentive listener

- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

Sales Representative- 07/2003 to 06/2004

Mobi Lobi, Bitola

Selling products and services using solid arguments to prospective customers. Performing cost-benefit analyses of existing and potential customers. Maintaining positive business relationships to ensure future sales.

Customs broker- 10/2015 to 09/2018

Vlastosped Bitola, Bitola

Working as a link between the customers and the relevant agencies my main goal is to manage and satisfy the three parties that are participating in the process. Huge experience in a customs entry environment. Strong experience in International transportation and freight forwarding on the land, ocean, and air. Excellent competence in Harmonised tariff schedule and efficient user of the SOCDAD system of customs data software.

Head at Customs broker office- 09/2018 to 04/2019

DB Schenker Skopje, branch Bitola

As continued my work as a head customs broker in the branch office of DB Schenker in the town of Bitola, North Macedonia my responsibilities were greater and included:

- ✓ Help client goods meet state requirements governing import and export and act as a liaison between clients and the relevant agencies.
- ✓ Assess commercial documents to see if they are compliant with regulatory requirements, prior to their submission.
- ✓ Governed under compliance with trade laws and regulations issued and enforced by the customs service of Republic North

Macedonia.

- ✓ Oversight of the day-to-day projects, coordinating and providing directions to the team colleagues
 - **Courier driver last mile logistics** -11/21 to 08/22

Go Express, Mannheim

Education

• Elementary school teacher

Faculty of Teachers and Educators Saint Kliment Ohridski University Bitola, North Macedonia

Linguistic

Public high school "Taki Daskalo" Bitola , North Macedonia

Recon Unit

Served in the Macedonian army Skopje and Kicevo, Macedonia

References

- **-Mr. Oliver Vucinic -** Head manager of the customs service for the southwest region of Macedonia; Phone No. 070/339-668;
- -Mr. Petar Trendafilovski- Chief at customs service branch in Bitola; Phone No. 070/237-030:
- -Mr. Aleksandar Petrovski- Customs officer; Phone No. 071/294-041;
- -Mr. Goran Minovski-Manager at DB Schenker Skopje;
- ++389 70 234133;